# ODUBO TARI FREZUOGHA

# ELECTRICAL ENGINEERING GRADUATE / FRONTEND WEB DEVELOPER

Okaka, Yenagoa, Bayelsa

080 6639 2197

tariodubo@gmail.com

#### PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

First class graduate of Electrical/Electronic Engineering with a knack for solving complex problems and an abnormally high level of attention to detail. Was introduced to programming for the first time in my second year during my undergraduate studies. There were so many other courses to study for at the time so I went into programming full time after graduation and I really love it. Continuously working and learning everyday to get better and have experience.

#### PERSONAL INFORMATION

State of Origin: Bayelsa Date of Birth: 6th March, 1997

#### EDUCATION

### **B.Eng Electrical/Electronic Engineering**

Niger Delta University, Wilberforce Island, Bayelsa

2015 - 2021

#### WORK EXPERIENCE

# Frontend Web Development Intern Encentral Solutions Limited, Jabi Abuja.

- Build responsive and elegant web Uls with bleeding edge HTML/CSS specs, advance JavaScript libraries and similar technology
- Design, Develop, Test, Deploy, Maintain and improve software applications
- Redesign UIs and implement new UIs.
- Responsible for integration of backend services.

#### **Bayelsa State Ministry of works and Infrastructure**

 Responsible for Design, Supervision and Inspection of projects.

# September 2021 - August 2022

April, 2022 - September, 2022

### **Engineering Intern**

## Yokogawa Nigeria Limited, Ikorodu Lagos.

- Took on the role of a Distributed Control System Engineer on intern projects.
- Responsible for writing control logic for programmable logic controllers.

August, 2019 - November, 2019